

CONTACT

1-G-9/8 Nazimabad no 1 Karachi



0330-2003614



syed.muhammadusman03@gmail.com

Adobe Photoshop

Figma

Adobe XD

Adobe Illustrator

LANGUAGES





HOBBIES









Syed. Muhammad Usman

UI/UX Designer



PROFILE

I am Creative UI/UX Designer. With 4 years of experiece, always keen on learning new design elements and appling them to my concept which help me in becoming a successful Graphic Designer. High skilled in website Designing, UI/UX, Typography & Photography with a mastry of Adobe Photoshop, Ilustrator & Figma. Holdig a great deal of knowlegde about leading the projects with teams and becoming the gel of the organization.



EDUCATION

Intermediate

Karachi Board Complete

Matric

Karachi Board Complete



EXPERIENCE

Syscrowd

Sr-UI/UX Designer 2024 - Present

► Tech Mind Ventures

2023 - 2024 Mid-UI/UX Designer

Salsoft Technologies

UI/UX Designer 2022 - 2023

Concept.co

Graphic Designer 2020 - 2021

Prolaxies

UI Designer 2019 - 2020



PORTFOLIO

behance.net/syedmuusman1